# **Zachary Morin**

# Web Developer

380 Pinellas Bayway Apt. C Tierra Verde, FL 33715 (727) 741-3424 zmorin15@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

Developer, problem-solver, creative type. Working primarily as a Front-End Developer with experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Node.js and WordPress. Consistently working to improve technical abilities and stay up to date on the latest development trends.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Socius Marketing, Tampa, FL - JR. Web Developer

July 2019 - PRESENT

- Review, manage, support and update existing code to websites.
- Update WordPress themes to perform client edits such as:
  - Implementing Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) and Custom Post
    Types to make themes fully customizable
  - Implementing new sections to client websites with design mocks provided by the design team
  - Integrating potential leads from web forms into client CRMs via webhooks
  - Create and update landing pages and microsites that are focused on paid advertisements

#### Socius Marketing, Tampa, FL - Intern Developer

May 2019 - July 2019

- Work with the development team at Socius Marketing, a fast-paced internet marketing agency that focuses on lead generation and search engine optimization. During this internship, responsibilities will include:
  - Maintain existing client websites by introducing new features to increase user engagement
  - Add, edit, and remove content from existing websites and/or development sites
  - Identify standardization approaches that may benefit entire development team
  - Quality check websites to ensure proper user experience, browser compliance, and cross-device compatibility

## **EDUCATION**

**St. Petersburg College, St. Petersburg FL** - Associate in Science, A.S Web Development

Jan 2017 - Jan 2019

Core classes included HTML & CSS, Intro to Programming, JavaScript, Client-side JavaScript, Server-side JavaScript (Node.js), Website building with PHP, and advanced PHP.

### **AWARDS**

Received Web Development Specialist Certificate from St.Petersburg College